새 프로그램 정보
New Program Information
1990년, 지구의 평화를 지키기 위해 왔다.
In the year 1990, they came to protect the peace of the Earth..
용자 엑스카이저!
Yuusha Exkaiser!
내 이름은 엑스카이저.
My name is Exkaiser.
우주 해적 가이스터로부터 지구를 지키기 위해 온 우주 경찰이다.
I am a space police, and I came to protect the Earth from the space pirates Geisters.
우주 해적 가이스터는 우주의 평화를 파괴하고, 보물이란 보물은 전부 빼앗는 참으로 나쁜 놈들이다.
Space pirates Geisters are the truly bad ones who destroy the peace of the Space, and steal all the treasures that you can think of.
그리고 이번에 놈들의 목표는 지구의 보물을 빼앗는 것.
Their objective this time is to steal the treasures of the Earth.
그렇지만 걱정 마라. 우리 우주 경찰 카이저스가 너희 지구를 지켜 보이겠다.
But do not worry. We, the space police Kaisers, will protect your Earth.
나, 엑스카이저는 보통은 코우타 군 집의 차로 모습을 바꾸며 지낸다.
I, Exkaiser, usually stay transformed as a car in Kouta's house.
그렇지만 우주 해적 가이스터가 나타나기만 한다면, 엑스카이저로 변형해서, 지구의 평화를 지키기 위해 용감히 싸운다.
But whenever space pirates Geisters appear, I transform into Exkaiser, and fight valiantly to protect the peace of the Earth..
계속 등장: 카이저스의 동료들
Now appearing: The comrades of Kaisers
그럼 우리 우주 경찰 카이저스의 동료를 소개한다.
Now, let me introduce our comrades of space police Kaisers.
엑스카이저로 변형한 나는, 게다가 대형 트레일러, 킹 로더하고 거대합체해서 킹 엑스카이저가 된다.
Transformed into Exkaiser, I combine further by doing Giant Fusion with a large trailer named King Loader.
다음은 레이커 브라더스를 소개한다.
Next, let me introduce Raker Brothers to you.
동해도 신칸센 로봇 블루 레이커.
Tokaido Shinkansen Robot: Blue Raker.
동북 신칸센 로봇 그린 레이커.
Tohoku Shinkansen Robot: Green Raker.
게다가 좌우합체해서 울트라 레이커가 된다.
Moreover, they perform Left Right Fusion to become Ultra Raker.
그리고 맥스 팀의 3인.
The next are the three members of Max Team.
제트 전투기 로봇 스카이 맥스.
Fighter Jet Robot: Sky Max.
레이싱 카 로봇 대시 맥스.
Racing Car Robot: Dash Max.
드릴 전차 로봇: 드릴 맥스.
Drill Tank Robot: Drill Max.
게다가 3체합체해서 갓 맥스가 된다.
Moreover, they perform Triple Fusion to become God Max.
2월 3일 토요일 저녁 5시 30분부터 시작하는 애니메이션.
(오사카 지구는 2월 2일 금요일)
Starting on Feburary 3rd Saturday, 17:30.
(Feburary 2nd Friday for Osaka)
용자 엑스카이저에서 우리 활약을 기대해 줘라.
Look forward to our roles at Yuusha Exkaiser.